This series is crafted for the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, behaviours, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Prom's close companion.
Must've the one who broke into
Luang Sanong's mansion last night.
Now it's certain that Prom is associated with the party.
Khun Prom know Pra Nai best, you're perfect for this.
Please stop this.
Do not disappoint father anymore than this.
I love you Kaewta.
Even though I'm not the beautiful lady?
I still insist that love is love.
Kaew! What happened? Are you okay?
Khun Yai, Saan where are you right now?.
Please be safe out there.
Khun Yai and I won't die so easily like that, Nanny.
Father.
Brother!
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Where have you been, Brother?
And where did you get those clothes from?
Where were you, son? Why didn’t you come home?
I had something urgent to take care of.
Is that so?
Yes, Father.
Next time, please send someone to inform us first, Brother. We were worried sick about you.
I’ll send my servant next time.
I’m glad you’re all right.
Yes, Father.
♫ Let my thought of you drifted along the wind ♫
♫ Carrying with it my love to the very far-end ♫
♫ With faint smell of flowers in the air ♫
♫ Hoping it’d reach that person waiting on the other side ♫
♫ Sending all my love through the air ♫
♫ I miss you so much more than you can imagine ♫
♫ Just want you know I don’t want anything ♫
♫ You don’t have to return the feelings if you don’t want to ♫
♫ May the wind carry this song…♫
♫…in my heart to you ♫
♫No matter for how long, I’ll always love you ♫
♫I’ll love you…until the time is through ♫
[Interminable]
Khun Yai, do you think Khun Prom will stop now?
I really can’t tell, Saen.
But I do hope he will.
That man, has regained consciousness?
Not yet, sir. The doctor said
he’s in a coma and might not make it.
If we can’t get the namelist of those traitors, our work might become more difficult.
What should we do then?
I must inform our people at the palace about their movements first.
Kan! Kan!
What’s the matter, Kaew?
Can you teach me the sword move?
I used to ask you so many times to practise it with me.
How come you want to do it today?
It’s just in case…
In case?
Enough with the questions. Come on then.
Fine, I won’t go easy on you.
Geez, you can’t even hold it right.
Uncle.
Good evening.
Bless you, dear. What matter has brought you here?
Are you sure, Som?
Yes, Miss.
People at the market are talking that Khun Phra Nai is infatuated with a dancer at Luang Sanor’s place.
A dancer at Luang Sanor’s place?
Lady Sophee is here to select dancers to perform at the Queen Mother’s ceremony.
Go on and pick anyone you like.
Thank you, Uncle.
Miss, that’s a guy not a girl.
This girl…
Kaew, there’s a show performing over there. Let’s go see it.
I’ll have this one.
Thank you very much, Miss.
Can you please help pick the rest for me, Uncle?
Of course. Kan and Kaew, you two should also go with Ruedee.
Yes, sir.
Why wasting your time, Miss? Just slap her in the face,
teach her a lesson and I’m sure she won’t mess with Khun Phra Nai again.
For a girl who doesn’t know her place and tries to seduce my man,
do you really believe just a slap is enough?
What if she runs to him and plays victim to make him pity her even more?
Or worse, what would I do if she tries to make him hate me?
You’re right, Miss. How clever of you.
Brother!
Sophee.
I want to let you know that the Queen Mother has kindly chosen me…
to be in charge of the ceremony for her.
Earlier, I went to Uncle’s place to pick the dancers to perform at the event.
You went to see Uncle? Which dancers have you picked?
I believe they are Ruedee, Kan, and Kaewta.
That’s good. All of Uncle’s dancers are very talented.
Yes, indeed. I must be visiting Uncle’s place more often to watch the rehearsal.
Can you please come with me, Brother?
Of course. If I'm not busy, I’ll go with you.
Thank you, Brother.
I must be going then.
Miss, why would you invite him too?
I want to be sure if that girl is the dancer people are talking about.
Som.
Yes, Miss?
Have you done what I told you to do?
I already told Lady Sophee about Khun Phra Nai being infatuated with the dancer,
at Luang Sanor’s place –exactly as you’ve ordered, Master Prom.
She has now found a way to deal with that dancer.
Good. You did well.
Follow up on this and keep me informed about it. You can go now.
Is that all, sir?
What else do you want?!
That’s all, sir.
What are you thinking, sir? Why did you ask her to tell Lady Sophee that?
That brat already knew about us. We can’t stick to our old plan now.
If he’s dead, his people will have a reason to attack us.
That’s why Chief has told me to do something to keep him distracted…
while Chief and the association are working on a big plan.
I see.
If Khun Phra Nai is busy with something else, he wouldn’t have time to investigate on us.
And we’d be able to do things more easily.
That’s right.
Once our job is done, I won’t have to be afraid anymore that Father might find out about it.
Because by then,
history shall have my name written as one of the people who has led this reform.
Kaewta dances so beautifully, Uncle.
Yes, he’s my best student.
Hello, Uncle.
Oh, you also came?
I’ve asked him to come and watch the rehearsal together.
Sophee is quite meticulous. She wants me to help ensure the performance would be perfect.
But I believe your dancers already look utterly beautiful…
I mean, they’re already doing so well I wouldn’t have to worry about it.
I’m certain now that I’ve picked the right person, Som.
Yes, Miss.
Kaew.
Khun Yai.
Are you going home?
Yes.
I’ll go with you.
You can’t. Someone might see us and get the wrong idea.
How wrong? I’d say they’re right.
Khun Yai…
Kaew.
I miss you so much.
Please stop. Let’s not make it more complicated.
Kaew.
I know you’re scared.
I used to be like that too.
Do you think I’ve never tried to restrain myself?
I’ve done it all, Kaew. And had my heart almost torn into pieces.
I can’t stop loving you, Kaewta.
Khun Yai…
Don’t you find it painful?
Look into my eyes and answer me.
Tell me if you can restrain yourself without feeling any pain, then I’ll let you go.
Kaew…
Yes, I don’t feel anything. It doesn’t hurt at all.
Liar.
I can’t help it if you don’t believe me.
Kaew…Kaew…
If both of us shall be suffering from love,
wouldn’t it be better to fight for it and go through the suffering together…
instead of going through it while hiding our feelings as if they were a sin?
Kaew, are you up yet?
Huh? Kaew?
What’s wrong, Mother Chan?
I can’t find Kaew anywhere, dear.
Kaew!
- Kaew!
- Can you hear me?
- My baby.
- Kaew.
- Kaew! Can you hear me?
- My baby.
Kaew. Kaew.
The incense stick has probably burnt out for quite some time.
- My baby.
- He’s not responding at all.
What should we do?
So beautiful.
I’m warning you, Saen. If you only keep looking but not making any move,
someone else might come and snatch the flower you’ve been admiring one day.
A widower with a kid like me wouldn’t dare to reach out for such a beautiful flower.
As long as you believe it in your heart,
even a dewdrop in the midst of a morning ray shall cast a reflection more beautiful than the sunrise itself.
A dewdrop will soon disappear after the sunrise.
But I do believe your sincerity will overcome all obstacles.
Look at Khun Phra Nai, Miss. His eyes have never left that Ruedee girl.
What do you think, Sophee?
How elegant indeed. I’ve never seen anyone who could dance so gracefully like your dancers, Uncle.
I’ve made the right decision to ask for your help.
Really? You’re not saying it just to please an old man like me, are you?
Let’s ask my brother then. Don’t you think so too, Brother?
I also agree with Sophee, Uncle.
Your dancers can dance so beautifully and gracefully more than any dancers I’ve seen in the city.
I’m glad to hear that indeed.
So, shall we stop here and let them get some rest? They’re probably exhausted now.
All right, off you go then.
I’ve prepared some food and desserts for them too.
How is it? Do you find it to your liking?
It’s delicious. But I like it more flavorful though.
Do most elites prefer food like this?
You should be thankful. How lucky we are to be able to eat something from Chao Phraya Narubodin’s place.
To be honest, Lady Sophee is quite nice, isn’t she?
Not like the rumor I’ve heard.
Where are Kaew and Kan?
Those two are busy moving musical instruments.
Have they eaten?
Don’t worry, those guys already took their portion of the food to that side.
I see.
Hey, Lady Sophee wants to talk to you.
Me?
Hmm.
Yes.
Oh dear, come sit up here. I don't mind at all.
I’m afraid I can’t, Miss.
Just do as you’re told.
I wouldn’t dare, Miss.
Let her be then, Miss.
She’s someone who knows her place after all.
Is there something you wish to talk to me, Miss?
I made you desserts.
Thank you, Miss. How fortunate of me.
Seeing that you’ve practised so hard, she’d like to give you some encouragement.
It’s my brother's favourite. He asked me to learn how to do it.
So that one day when we get married, I could…
A perfect housewife for Khun Phra Nai. Is that right, Miss?
Oh, don’t say that.
Aww, who else in this city wouldn't know that you’re his fiancé, Miss?
Try it, Ruedee.
It’s so beautiful I wouldn’t dare to eat it, Miss.
Stop being so pretentious…I mean, just do as you’re told.
Apart from my brother, I’d like to know if other people will also find this dessert to their liking.
Yes, Miss.
How is it? Do you like it?
This rascal! She’s asking you, why aren’t you answering? So rude.
It’s you who are rude, Som. Don’t you see her mouth is still full of food? How would she be able to talk?
Oh, you’re right, Miss.
So, do you like my dessert?
What happened, Miss Ruedee?
Is that blood?
What happened?
Glass shards?
Serve her right. She won’t be able to eat anything for a while, Miss.
This is just a warning. If she keeps pestering my man, it’ll be worse.
That’s right, Miss. For someone who doesn’t know her place, she really deserves it.
Where’s my brother, though?
I have no idea, Miss. I’ve been right by your side all this time.
Kaew, come downstairs once you’re done. They’re waiting for you to eat together.
Yes, Dum.
Khun Yai, what are you doing here?
Kaew, I miss you so much.
Kaew.
This is a chamber for the dancers, Miss.
Wait. Have you seen Khun Phra Nai?
No, Miss.
Please excuse me.
Geez, servants here are not helpful at all.
They should have helped looking for him first.
Let’s go, Som.
Yes, Miss.
Sophee.
What are you doing here, Brother?
I’m here to see how Uncle has kept his instruments.
Is that so?
But I can’t see any instrument here, Miss.
Kaewta…
Are you looking for me, Sophee?
Kaewta and the others were cleaning the instruments when I came here.
I was so engrossed with the conservation that I forgot the time completely.
I see. Kaewta must be very fun to talk with, so much that you even forget about me.
I’m getting quite offended now.
It’s not like that, Miss. We were only talking about…
about Uncle, Miss.
Yes. I told him about that time when I learnt how to play treble fiddle with Uncle.
Back then, Uncle was very strict.
There was once when I sneaked out to hang around and got caught.
Uncle punished me by having me clean all the instruments here.
I also got punished like that.
I see. Both of you were actually gossiping about your teacher.
But why did you shut the door though?
You wouldn’t have called it ‘gossiping’ then.
True that.
Please excuse me then.
Yes.
Kaewta can dance so beautifully. That’s why he’s Uncle’s best student, isn’t he?
Even though he’s a man, right, Miss?
Yes.
How are you feeling?
Better now. The bleeding has stopped.
Have you done anyting to upset Lady Sophee?
Is she upset with me?
But those glass shards in the dessert…
I suppose she must have accidentally dropped them in the dessert she made for me.
Perhaps, she didn’t mean it, Saen.
Do you really believe that?
Lady Sophee is very nice to me. She treats me as if I were her friend.
She probably didn’t know there were glass shards in the dessert.
But that doesn’t sound like Lady Sophee that I know at all.
What do you mean, Saen?
It’s nothing.
Anyway, maybe it’d be better for you to try to steer clear of her.
Why are you telling me this?
Well, I’m…
…worried about you.
Ruedee!
Yes, Kaew?
Oh, you’re here too?
Yes, Khun Kaew.
Is there something wrong?
- Nothing, Kaew!
- Nothing!
But why are you two…
There’s really nothing.
Thank you, Saen. I’m going then.
Yes.
Let’s go, Kaew.
- But I think there’s something going on between...
- It’s really nothing. Let’s go.
Kaew, I’m not going to lose you to anyone. I’ll do it today.
‘I’m worried about you…’
Worried about you?
Geez, Kaew. I’m not going to tell you next time.
Kan! I thought you’d already gone home.
Kaew, I have something to talk to you.
Well then, I’ll head home first. I have to go help Mum in the kitchen.
Yes.
Do you like it here?
I never thought it’d look so pretty in the evening.
So, what is it that you want to talk to me, Kan?
Well, I…I…
Why are you stuttering? Just say it.
This little brother is always here to listen to you.
Do you only see me as your brother?
Of course, why are you asking that?
If you really see me as your brother, will you take heed of a warning from this brother of yours?
What do you warn me about?
About Khun Phra Nai.
What about him?
You have feelings for him, don’t you?
What did you say? They’re planning to assassinate His Majesty?
A betrayal member has admitted that to the commanding officer of the Engineer Bridgae, King’s Royal Guard.
A betrayal member? Who is he?
[A few days earlier]
It’s Luang Sinad Yotaruk, Father.
Luang Sinad Yotaruk…
It’s you.
Yes, sir.
Luang Sinad Yotaruk.
He probably got chosen by a lucky draw. That’s why he was so scared.
Yes, Father. Since he was too scared to do it himself,
he decided to confess to His Serene Highness Prince Punthaprawat.
At least he still has some guts.
What’s next then?
When His Serene Highness Prince found out about it,
he went straight to inform His Royal Highness Prince Chakrabongse Bhuvanath.
They are now conducting a secret investigation.
Good heavens, our holy Buddha is still guarding over our country after all.
Otherwise, I’m afraid there might have been more bloodshed.
No one else knows about this except us, Father. Please keep it between us only.
An important information like this shouldn’t be leaked out to anyone, including those in our household.
And one more thing, Father. I’d like you to talk to Prom.
Talk to him about what?
I’m afraid he hasn’t thought it through and still associated himself with those people.
It might eventually cause him trouble.
Maybe you’re over worried about it, son. Prom can’t handle anything important like that.
But I’ll try talking to him for you.
Thank you, Father.
Freedom doesn’t fall from the sky!
It’s something we have to reach out, and grab it with our own hands!
It’s time for our voice to be heard all over the city!
This meeting is very important.
That’s why all of us here should drink an oath of allegiance, like what the palace people often do,
in order to prove our sincerity and honesty. I hope everyone will agree to it.
May this blood be our witness, and this water an oath.
May tonight be a shining light that will lead us to a change!
Drink it to swear an oath of loyalty to our ideology.
That we will never betray each other, even if it means death!
Let’s drink it!
Cheers!
here the absolute monarchy.
Here, the absolute monarchy!!!
What's troubling you?
It's nothing.
Then here's how I shall open your mouth.
Kaew!
Mom!
I was worried so nothing.
Turns out Rudee just ran away with her lover.
Rudee? With her lover?
Khun Yai.
You...
So you're still here.
I have a flavor to ask you.
Do you think Prom will stop, sir?
I really can't tell, Sin.
What should we do?
Dace practice, then sword practice.
Incase we need it.
Stop asking so many questions, come!
Then we slash, slash, slash, slash.
I got chosen. I was so happy.
I'll get to dance infront of Pra Phan Pi Ruang.
But no, I was chosen for...
For what? Stay tuned.
I can't tell you.
But it's definitely not good.
So no need to be sad if you're not chosen.
Today is an amazing day
because I finished early again.
Because I have to talk with Kaewta at Mae Payom's house.
It's a deep talk, that's why we can't talk at Luang Sanor.
That's why we have to talk at...
That scene.
Which scene.
I talk here and it's inappropriate.
I have to talk at your house.
I'm not a fighter but a lover.
Only action I'm having is with Keawta.
Those action all day all night.
What is this scene about?
Just having conversation.
Resolving.
Because...
We haven't resolved anything since episode 1.
This is the opportunity.
Softly.
Level 5.
Stay tune.
♫ A flower…when blooming ♫
♫ Its fragrance still fills the air…even after a long time ♫
♫ No matter how much time has passed ♫
♫ I can still remember traces of love and kisses you left in my heart ♫
♫ Still miss all those times, even when our love can never be the same ♫
♫ But I can never forget about us ♫
♫ No matter how much time has passed ♫
♫ I’m still the same, still missing you with all my heart ♫
♫ Every time when the night is falling ♫
♫ My mind keeps worrying how you are doing ♫
♫ No matter how much time has passed ♫
♫ I’m still the same, still missing you with all my heart ♫
♫ Every time when the night is falling ♫
♫ My mind keeps worrying how you are doing♫
♫ No matter how much time has passed ♫
[Interminable]
[Idolfactory]
[IQIYI]